franchisemart.in 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Franchise Mart

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### **The Information we collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the **[Franchise Mart](http://www.franchisemart.in/franchise/vikram-bakshi-offers-buy-mcdonalds-franchise-stake/ "Vikram Bakshi offers to buy out McDonald’s franchise stake")** website. On some pages, you can make requests and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number

### **The way we use Information:**

You can register with our website if you have questions, concerns, or would like to receive more information on our company. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### **Our commitment to Data Security:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### **How you can access or correct your Information?**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain online. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### **How to contact us?**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please write to us at[ info@franchisemart.in](mailto:info@franchisemart.in)  
**call on: 09909960054**
